ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/105
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Statement before Health Needs of the Nation, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Presented by William Ross, the manager of the Philadelphia dress joint board.
- Swiss Tariff-Cutting Hypothesis, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  Report studying the trade and employment effects under this hypothesis.
- Temporary National Economic Committee, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  Final statement of Senator Joseph C. O'Mahoney, Chairman.
- Textile/Apparel Steering Group, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  Statement of Shelley Appleton, Secretary Treasurer.
- United States Department of Commerce, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Statements
- United States Trade Versus Common Market Trade (Box 4, Folder 52)
  Comparisons of textile and apparel exports and imports. Undated.
- Urban Wage Rate, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  Report entitled "The Present Status and Proposed Conversion of the Urban Wage Rate Series."
- Welcome to Chiang-Mai, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  By the U.S. Textile Delegation. Includes business cards, a newspaper, and other miscellany.
- Wholesale and Consumer Price Indexes, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  Correspondence form Teper to Geoffrey H. Moore, the commissioner of the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
- Publications (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Various.
- The Living Wage, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  Presented by W. Jett Lauck before the United States Railroad Labor Board. Three parts.
- Economic Conditions and Impact of Imports [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  November 16, 1967. 2 copies
- Economic Conditions and Impact of Imports [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  November 16, 1967. 3rd copy
- Welfare Plans, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Item 807.00 of the Tariff Schedules of the United States and the Apparel Industry, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  May, 1970. 2 copies
- Statement of David Dubinsky, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare. February 25, 1947
- Address by David Dubinsky., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Annual Meeting of the National Executive Board of the National Coat and Suit Recovery Board. February 5, 1959
- Aspects of Industrial Homework in the Apparel Trades, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  July, 1941
- Femme-Lines, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Sept-Oct. 1968; July-Aug. 1972.
- Long-Term Changes in Employment, Payrolls, and Earnings 1939-1959, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  January 26, 1960; August 22, 1960 (2 copies); March 15, 1966
- Women's Garment Industry in Canada: The Past Decade and Current Outlook, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  April 28, 1961. 2 copies.
- Unit Production of Women's Apparel, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  3 copies
- In Opposition to Duty Reductions on Articles of Women's and Children's Apparel, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  July 21, 1975
- Apparel (Knit and Woven) Imports Under the Provisions of Item 807.00 of the Tariff Schedules of the United States, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  April 17, 1975
- Domestic Apparel Industry: Economic Background and the Impact of Imports, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Giustizia, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Italian
- The Actuary, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  v.2:no.7 (1968:Sept.)
- The New York Statistician, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  v.21:no.4 (1970:Mar./April); v.21:no.5 (1970:May/June)
- International Trade, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Documentary Material before the U. S. Tariff Commission (Box 5, Folder 20)
  2 copies
- Economic Changes: Puerto Rico, 1938-1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Commerce Department Press Release, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Comparative Analysis of Cost and Prices of Identical Rayon Dresses, 1939-1948 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- National Bureau of Economic Research, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Mental Arithmetic of Messrs. Schreier and Wood, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Puerto Rico Minimum Wage (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Social Security Benefits, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Research Department (Box 5, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Management Engineering Department, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- United States Tariff Commission, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Activities of the ILGWU Research Department, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- U. S. Apparel Firms that send Cut Work Abroad (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Memorandum on the Measurement of Changes in the Cost of Living, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Employment Statistics, 1954-1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Measurement of Prices, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Price Statistics Review Committee, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Price Statistics Review Committee, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Impact of Imports on the Women's Garment Industry, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- News From ACWA and ILGWU, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- ILGWU Tells House Committee Now Is Time to Shorten Workweek to 35 Hours, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- United Nations Statistical Commission, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Statistics and Politics, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Memorandum to Royal Commission on Canadian Economic Prospects, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Increased Minimum Wages for the Puerto Rican Needle workers, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Orphaned Pages (Box 5, Folder 45)